Thanks for your work!
I'm very happy to be able to see you at the Hallo! Stee, this time with Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and,
Ilia Lisa from Juice-Juice.
We will be presenting this time with these two,
Please stay with us until the end.
Now, let's take a look at Morning Musume。 23 and Juice-Juice are in the middle of their spring tour.
We are currently in the middle of our spring tour with Morning Musume。 On May 3, the date of this "Halo!
Morning Musume。 23 will perform in Osaka,
Juice-Juice will be in Fukuoka.
Thank you very much to everyone who came to the concert.
We are in the middle of our spring tour,
Juice-Juice is celebrating their 10th anniversary and Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。's 25th anniversary,
What is the content of the tour?
What are the contents of the tour?
Yes, we are going to look back on the 10th anniversary from the past,
I think it's going to be a very nice tour that will allow us to look back on our 10th anniversary from the past,
And the costumes are really cute.
The costumes are cute.
The costumes are really cute, so I hope people will pay attention to that as well.
Morning Musume。 23 is my favorite Morning Musume。 23 has been around for 25 years, and I think there must have been a time in my life when I took the entrance exam for the group,
I think there must have been a time like that,
I'm sure there must have been such a time in your life, but no matter which Morning Musume。 I think that no matter which Morning Musume。ヌs group you are attached to, you will enjoy this tour,
If you have been exposed to Morning Musume。 I hope that those who have been exposed to Morning Musume。
I'm looking forward to seeing you both.
Morning Musume。 23 will perform in Shizuoka on May 4, Okayama on May 5, and Saitama on May 7.
How about Juice-Juice?
Juice-Juice will perform in Hiroshima on May 4, Kanagawa on May 6, and Aichi on May 7.
And as the culmination of this tour, we will be performing at the Nippon Budokan on May 29,
I would be very happy if you could come and see us.
We are looking forward to seeing many of you during this period, and we hope you enjoy yourselves.
Please take a look at this video first.
Here you go!
Are you happy?
It's too late, I can't do the jogi of love.
It's too late, today's today's today's today's today's today's today's
It's too late. It was a surprise the other day.
It's too late. You had a reaction.
More just me.
Show me some proof of love.
I'm not sure I can do it, but...
I want to be happy.
I want to nurture love
He's good, he's good, he's good, he's good, he's good
He's all she's got, he's all she's got
I like her, I like her, I like her
Let me out of here
I love her so much, I miss her so much
Are you happy?
I love her so much
I'm gonna miss you so much.
After being with you...
I'm so anxious.
It's too late.
You'll never be ready for love
It's too late
Today's the day
The surprise the other day
It's too late.
You had a reaction.
Hey, come on.
You can't make reservations about love.
Come on.
Tomorrow is tomorrow.
Hey, come on. Come on.
For next year's birthday.
Head on over.
Love me all you want.
Thanks for watching.
Morning Musume。' 23's Sakura Oda and,
Juice-Juice's Iryu Lisa, who is a member of Halo! STE' 23 and Juice-Juice's Irisa.
From here I would like to tell you a little bit about each other.
I will ask you some questions, so let's answer them in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
Yes, I will. Please do.
What made you happy recently when you received a compliment?
My performance at the Hina Fest.
What are you working on most right now?
Vocalization.
It will be two years in two months since you joined Juice-Juice.It will be two years in two months since you joined Juice-Juice.
What was the most shocking experience?
How quickly rehearsals progressed.
The review of the tour with Chief Fugetsu.
What was the most memorable moment for you as a team?
The chorus and rehearsals.
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
Which song arrangement is your favorite?
Komushi Factory's
Dosukoi: Humble and Bold
I see.
Thank you very much.
Lisa, it's been two years, hasn't it?
I am surprised myself.
Time passes so fast.
Was the rehearsal early?
It felt so fast,
For me, rehearsal itself
I think it was the first time for me.
It was the first time for me to have a rehearsal.
It was my first time,
I didn't even understand how it works,
That's right.
I didn't know how a rehearsal would go.
I didn't know how the rehearsals were going to go,
And the senior members of the same group...
Akari Uemura was the only senior member of the same group,
I was also nervous about being surrounded by other senior members of the same group.
I was very nervous,
I was really worried at the time,
I was really worried,
I was crying a lot.
I remember that very well,
But Mr. Oda taught me how to hold the microphone,
And I also had a part in the chorus piece with Oda-san,
He would check the melody for me,
Thank you very much.
I miss it.
Let me ask you one more question.
What made you happy when you were praised?
What made you happy?
I sang with Reine Inoue as a duo.
I sang "TOMORROW WILL BE TENKI NARU" with Reine Inoue as a duo,
This song is by Conch Factory, so it has been a long time since Inoue sang it.
So it was also the first time for Inoue-san to sing this song in a very long time,
And of course it was the first time for me to sing this song,
I wondered how everyone would react to it.
When it was over, they really praised me,
But when it was over, I received so many compliments,
It was a great relief,
It was a great relief, and I was very happy.
This is only my second year, so I am sure I will feel many more things from now on.
Questions for WANASORE were asked after the VTR.
Hello! sta.
Are you ready?
Seino
Let's tie our arms around each other, let's call forth a miracle!
Beyond the New Single
Seek me, traveller of destiny
Now on sale
Beyond the New Single
Beyond the New Single Dreams Can't Even Be Drawn Into the Night Sky
Car
ah ni
Angulum
Angulum new album
Big Love
Now on sale!
Halo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Mr. Oda.
Please give me your best regards.
A little while ago, you released a photo book on your 24th birthday,
What did you do to prepare for the photo shoot?
A moderate diet.
What makeup trends are you interested in right now?
I am wondering why the trend is to use very light colors for eyeshadow.
What are you particularly conscious of during your current tour?
Being authentic.
How did you feel when you were chosen to do a commercial for Kentucky Fried Chicken?
I thought it was a dream.I thought it was a dream.
If you were to sing a duet in Hello!
I would like to sing a hot song composed by Odaomaki and Tsunku III.
Thank you very much.
I heard that you have released a photo book,
What about a moderate diet?
I have a moderate diet where I can eat anything until 6:00 or 7:00 p.m., or until 7:00 p.m. on days when I can't. I just don't eat at night,
I was on a diet where I just didn't eat at night,
I'm on a diet where I just don't eat at night, and I've been able to do that moderately.
I'm in.
I'm the opposite.
What about the rest?
What are you particularly conscious of on the tour?
Being authentic,
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。's 25 years of history,
There are a lot of different Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。 Even for one of the songs.
We were not the original members. We weren't even born back then.
So, it's like a cover.
I didn't want it to be like "Genki covered an old song,
We are the only Morning Musume。 We are the only Morning Musume,
We are the only Morning Musume。 I wanted to be able to say, "This is our song," as the real Morning Musume,
It's not just about the correctness of the choreography,
We are not only trying to get the choreography right, but we are also trying to be inspired by it.
It's wonderful.
Hallo! The next part of the show will continue after this.
Halo! Ste. 2012, May 20, 2012!
Here we go, Hello Kitchen!
I, Masashi Natsuyaki, will participate as a helper from this time.
And this time, this member is here.
Yes, I am Kisaki Karada of Juice-Juice.
This is my first Hello Kitchen, and I will do my best to make delicious food.
Please give me your best regards.
Sensei, please give me your regards.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm going to participate in Hello Kitchen as a helper from this time, so please give me your best regards, Sensei.
It's very reassuring to have a wonderful partner here.
I hope that I can be called a wonderful partner and that we can get to know each other better and better and make this a fun corner.
I have not been involved with Emada-chan for a long time,
This is the first time we are working together like this,
I hope we can have a good time cooking together.
Let's get started right away.
What would you like to cook this time?
Fluffy pancakes.
This one.
The best of the best.
Very special.
Okay, here are the ingredients for fluffy pancakes.
How do you like pancakes? Do you like them?
I love them so much. Me too.
Me too. They're good.
I think that's what you usually eat at restaurants this time,
But today, you will learn a lot from the teacher and make it by yourself,
I hope you'll do your best.
I'll do my best.
Let's get started.
What would you like to do first?
First of all, I would like to separate the eggs into yolks and whites.
We will make the dough separately.
I think we can do that.
Do you cook?
I cook every day.
That's great!
That's promising.
Have you ever made pancakes?
Yes, I have. Yes, I have,
But I was very young at the time,
I don't remember making them very well.
I made the egg yolk batter first,
The egg whites are kept cold in the refrigerator.
You want to flour the dough.
Today we will add 2 grams of baking powder.
This is ?
Light flour.
40 grams of flour.
Put it in here.
Mix.
Let's sift it.
Is it OK if I put all of it in?
It's a little hard to sift if you put it all in.
It feels like making candy.It feels like making candy.
Then, here's the sugar.
30 grams of sugar.
Put it in.
Let's mix it.
Next, we'll use 40 cc of milk for the yolks.
3 tablespoons.
Three tablespoons. Sorry.
Let's mix it well.
I have always liked this kind of mixing process the best when making sweets,
I like the mixing part in cooking as well,
When it was time to mix, I asked my mother to call me.
I've been doing it since I was a little girl.
Then, vanilla essence.
A drop.
Yes, I put it in.
Let's mix it.
If you put it in well, it will be lumpy, so divide it into about three times.
First one.
I put in the first drop.
I like this mixing part.
It looks fun. When I was making it.
I'm used to it.
You're used to it.
It's going really well.
There's not much to go into.
Now let's make the meringue.
Here's Miyamizu's point!
Add lemon juice to stabilize the meringue bubbles.
What does this mean?
Yes, what does it mean?
A pastry-making expert.
I have no idea about this one.
This is a bit more scientific,
Egg whites are a bit alkaline. A little.
By adding acidity, we can bring them to neutral.
This makes them stable.
It's hard to tell with such an alkaline acid,
Vinegar? I remember that if you add something acidic, it will make it square.
Oh, wow. Did you know that?
That's new to me.
Okay, egg whites, from the refrigerator.
I think it is better to put them on ice to make them stand up.
I think there are situations where you don't have ice, so keep them in the fridge as long as you can,
Let's make sure they are well healed.
First, just the egg whites.
First.
I like to use a medium speed, first.
I want them to be foamy, so I'm going to add the lemon juice.
I'm going to put it in, right, sir?
Don't put the seeds in.
Yes, I'll mix it soon.
This is also medium speed.
But you don't seem scared at all.
It looks totally familiar.
I'm used to it.
I just thought, I felt a little accustomed to the fact that you are using your left hand as well.
It's amazing. It's very difficult.
If you only use this hand, you can only do it like this.
By turning it around, you can make it work as a whole.
He has a little bit of skill.
That's amazing. You were doing it before the teacher told you.
That's amazing. When it starts to stand up a little bit, I put the sugar in two or three times.
Ten grams of granulated sugar.
Do you want to add half a gram?
Yes.
10 grams of granulated sugar.
I put it in.
It's a little bit square.
What do you think? How do you see it in this case?
It looks like it has a corner.
What do you think?
It's angular.
It's like the beak of a mouth.
Wow, that's great. It is.
I guess the lemon juice is in it, so it's stable.
I see.
It's so stable.
It makes me want to eat it as it is.
It's amazing. It's so fluffy.Amazing. Fluffy.
You can't mess with it too much, can you? It's so fluffy.
So, I'd like to continue with the dough.
Now, I would like to continue with the dough.
First, blend them in.
Blend them in.
The dough has a lot of white on it.
It is also good to do it with both hands.
Let's try a little.
Turn the whole ball.
Then it will come to the center.
It's a black technique.
It's getting fluffy, isn't it?
I think that's enough.
Let's go all the way.
This is the most important point.
You know what I mean.
You don't need it.
Don't cut it off.
Don't cut it off?
Here.
Mix it like this.
You mustn't crush it.
I mean from the bottom up.
Oh, great.
Like this.
If you cut it like this...
The fluffiness goes down.
It sinks.
It's okay if the mixture is uneven.
It's worse to squash air bubbles.
Be careful!
That's all for this time.
We'll finish it next time.
Please look forward to it!
Oh, wow!
Tip first, then the other end.
Tip first.
Mmm!
Mmmm hihi!
Something new is happening, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I will look forward to the completion of the cooking and also to the development.
Do you cook, Risa?
Yes, I do. I think I am a pretty good cook.
That's my impression.
I cook on my days off from work, for example,
Your mother will leave you this, this, and this,
Risa can make whatever she wants with them.
That's amazing. That's the hardest thing to do.
You don't have to do that?
But at home, we tend to use meat.
Pork or chicken is the most common,
But when it comes to the seasoning I like,
I like to season it a little bit like teriyaki.
But, as long as there is soy sauce, sugar, mirin, and sake, everything tastes good.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
What is your newest dish?
My newest dish is very simple,
My mom gave me pork, onions, and green peppers.
I used them to make this dish.
So I made a stir-fry with oyster sauce as the main ingredient.
It was absolutely delicious.
It was delicious.
I think people like that, like Risa, are the most amazing,
I can't do that, I can only cook with the enthusiasm to make this,
The skill I have acquired recently is chawanmushi (steamed egg custard).
It seems that it can be made in a microwave oven,
I can make it in a steamer, a pot, or a frying pan,
I have been researching the right amount of heat,
I've been researching the heat settings, and I've been thinking, "This way it's a little sudatsu (hairy),
I've been researching the heat level and how it should be, and I've found that this way it's a bit liquidy,
I've recently been researching the heat level and how to make it more "sudsy," or "a little liquidy," or "a little soft," or "a little soft and supple.
Yes, it is like that. That's how I feel.
Hello! STE!
Project has a lot of songs, but what are your favorite lyrics?
Project has many songs, do you have a favorite lyric?
I like Juice-Juice's song "Joryu".
It cheers me up a lot, and the tune is cute,It cheers me up immensely and the tune is cute,
I recommend this song when you feel down.
I, Sakura Oda, sing a song called "Smile, You're the Sunshine of the World,
Before the chorus of the second verse, the song says, "Adults must feel like it's not fair. The adults want to be you again. I received this song when I was in junior high school,
I felt completely differently about this song now as an adult than I did when I was in junior high school,
I would like all junior high school students to listen to this song one more time after they become adults.
Please watch the VTR.
Presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of Hello! Project songs that resonate with you and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms. This week, I, Minami Okamura, will present the song.
Let's start with a bang!
The glass slipper is in my hand, turn the pumpkin carriage to the front
Morning Musume。 It's the lyrics of a song about the beginning of your fantasy,
These are not two connected lyrics, but the first and second lyrics sung in the same melody,
I love fantasy, princesses, and movies like that,
I love fantasy, princesses, and movies like that, and this song is about waiting for a prince,
I have an image of a board princess waiting for a prince or a dream to come towards her,
But I thought the lyrics were about a strong woman who is willing to go out on her own, not solo,
I thought the lyrics were about a strong woman who is not a soloist, but is going out on her own, and that's what struck me,
I thought it was a very beautiful song because it showed the strength of a strong woman, but not in a manly way, but in a girlish way, while still going out on her own.
The way she expresses this strength in a fantastical way is very interesting.
I wondered if he was a very strict person,
But the title of the song is fantasy,
It's very dreamy,
Not too realistic to give up on his dream,
She is not too realistic and doesn't give up on her dreams, but rather she is determined to follow her dreams on her own feet, even in the midst of her idol activities,
I think I'm dreaming too much.
There are dreams that may be too big, but we are not too big.
But when you hear that we are going to make them come true, it makes you believe that we are going to make them come true.
It's so cute and exciting, and it really cheers me up.
I love this song very much.
Please look forward to the next installment!
Hallo! STE!
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and Juice-Juice's Irisa will be presenting the next episode of "Halo! STE!
As I mentioned in the opening, 2023 is the 25th anniversary of Morning Musume。 As I mentioned in the opening, the year 2023 marks the 25th anniversary of Morning Musume。
Now, Risa, as we enter the kingdom of history, is there anything that you would like to keep in mind?
Yes, I do. Even though the form of the group is changing rapidly, the songs will always be there.
So, I would like to keep those songs and sing them over.
I think the songs are the most important thing, and I always sing the songs with care,
Each song has its own life. I think each song has a life of its own. I know that each song has a life of its own, and I know that Risa-chan has her first Morning Musume song that she heard.
You will have to live with those memories,
I would like to keep that in mind as I go on with my life.
Then, have there been any turning points for you since you joined the group?
For me, it was last August 2022,
Due to some members' health problems, we had a live concert with only 6 members.
At that time, new members Sakira Ishiyama and Akari Yanagida had joined the group,
But they had not participated in the performance yet,
However, the live performance with six members was a big event for me, since we had been working as a resident group,
I was very excited, and I was rather nervous or anxious,
I was very nervous and rather anxious, but now that it's over, I feel that it was a great experience for me,
But after it was over, I think it was a great experience for me, and I think it was an event that brought me closer to my seniors.
There is a lot to learn, isn't there? I don't have any turning points.
I don't have a turning point,
So, I may divide myself into one thing at a time. In my mind.
I guess this time I'm talking with Risa-chan is a turning point for me, too.
I wonder. But maybe there is a big difference,
Project, I would like to learn more and more and do my best.
Juice-Juice
〜Jetickets by OfuMiku
I don't know, I feel a little bit like that... I'm going to stop saying that
I'll stop now, nothing will be said to me
Come on, live your life. It's hard sometimes.
Yes, we all cry
No more sleepless nights
Of course. Time is not infinite.
You're right. You can at least believe what you're feeling.
You just have to trust your feelings.
That's a good idea.
You know how many times I've failed at something?
Maybe next time it'll work out.
One more time. One more time. Get up.
Clench your fists and go.
Tomorrow's the weather
Conditions are bad so stay inside
But don't worry, tomorrow it's gonna be a beautiful sunny day
Thank you for watching
You know how many times I've failed?
Maybe next time you'll get it right
One more time, one more time, just get upOne more time, one more time, get up
I'm gonna put it in my fist and I'm gonna go.
I'm sorry I've been so rude to you so many times
♪ Somewhere there's a nice bird waiting for you
One more time, one more time Don't give up
Let's look up and walk
I'll be fine tomorrow
Subtitle: Kiyohiroi
You're doing your best, you're so cool
Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and
Ilyrisa of Juice-Juice, and the members of Halo! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement!
Project 2023 Spring City Circuit is now underway!
Morning Musume。 23 will be in Shizuoka on the 4th tomorrow
The day after tomorrow is Okayama
The day after tomorrow is Okayama, and May 7th is Saitama.
And Juice-Juice will be in Hiroshima on the 4th tomorrow
May 6 in Kanagawa Prefecture
May 7th will be in Aichi Prefecture!
This tour is not limited to this week.
Please check it out!
And Juice-Juice will perform in Japan on May 29th.
The culmination of this tour will be at Nippon Budokan on May 29th.
It will be the culmination of this tour, and we will be performing at the Nippon Budokan on May 29th, just 3 months after our last performance at the Budokan in the fall tour,
It is an experience that is not easy to come by, and I am truly grateful for the opportunity,
I hope that this experience will not be wasted and that everyone will enjoy the show.
I hope that this experience will not be wasted and that everyone will enjoy it.
Morning Musume。 23 will start Morning Musume。' on May 17. 22 25th Anniversary Concert Tour Sing into the Beat, which is the Budokan performance of Kaede Kaga's graduation special,
Blu-ray disc and DVD will be released.
I already feel nostalgic about the last appearance of Kaede Kaga and the last performance of Morning Musume,
I already feel nostalgic about it. I hope that this DVD and Blu-ray disc will be able to reach many people.
I hope that the "Halo! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
Project members. New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please be sure to subscribe to the channel.
We are still in the midst of a difficult time, but let's get through it together.
This time, we will be joined by Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 23's Sakura Oda and Juice-Juice's Risa Irie.
Farewell.
Thank you for watching.